securegatewayaccess.com 2011-05-19

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting SecureGatewayAccess.com. Your privacy is important to us, our online Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products and services with integrity in dealing with our customers. _Secure Gateway Access does not collect or use any information about you_ including, but not limited to, IP addresses or personal information and does not utilize cookies to collect any such information.

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect (or in our case, do not collect), use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our website, products and services. This Privacy Policy only applies to the information we collect through our website and does not apply to information we collect through other means or sources. By using or accessing our website, products or services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. Again, as a reminder, 

_Secure Gateway Access does not collect or use any information about you_

including, but not limited to, IP addresses or personal information and does not utilize cookies to collect any such information. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing including your name and email address, the URL for the website you visited, and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year.

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such revised policy with a new effective date. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of any such change. Instead you accept it as your affirmative responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of our website following the posting of a revised Privacy Policy with a new effective date indicates your agreement to the changes. 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please emails us at [cs@securegatewayaccess.com](mailto:cs@securegatewayaccess.com) or call us at 888-294-3151.
